viralwomen.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This document outlines our privacy guidelines, to which you agree by navigating this site. Regular updates of the privacy policy are completed, requiring you to check back on this policy from time to time. If not otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms have the meaning given to them in the Terms of Use (the “Terms”). 

Information We Collect: 

In order to use our Website and some of our Services, you may be required to register and provide us with certain Personal Information. We also collect Personal Information through your use of the Services generally and drom third paerty websites and services. “Personal Information” means information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number and expiration date, or information about activities directly linked to a person, such as that person’s location. Examples of the Personal Information that we collect from you include your name, location and e-mail address. You may register through your Facebook account and may choose to log in through the Facebook Connect Feature, Twitter or Google Plus. By doing so, you are asking those entities to send us certain information from your profile and authorize us to collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. It is your voluntary decision whether to provide us with any such Personal Information, but if you refuse to provide such information we may not be able to register you or allow certain uses of the Site and/or Services. 

You may provide information on behalf of another entity. If you completed the registration or provide information on behalf of a certain entity, you represent to us that you were authorized by that entity to give us consent to use the submitted information. 

User Content - Some Features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties. 

In addition, when you use the Website certain non-personally identifiable information may be automatically gathered about your IP address, geo-location information, mobile device, browser type, browser language or operating system. We may use third party contractors to collect and aggregate this information. For more information, please see Cookies. 

How we Protect Information 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our order form, our merchant services providers encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We will delete any information provided to us by a user upon the receipt of a written request by such user. We cannot restore information that we have deleted. 

How we Use Information 

We and our affiliates may use personal information provided to us to as follows: 

· To enable us to verify your credentials, in order to maintain reasonable security, provide developers with the information that is useful in developing new features and services for our users, allow us to potentially vary advertising based on user preference, usage preferences and demographics, enable us to develop and improve the features, contents, and services available, fulfill your requests for our Services, in connection with your use of the Site or Services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you our products or services that we believe may be of interest to you, to carry out transactions which you have requested, to enforce our rights and resolve disputes. 

· We will retain information transmitted to us in the context of use of Services for further internal use in connection with our efforts to improve our Services and products. 

We may use non-personally identifying information that we collect to provide statistical information about users of the Website or Services, to improve the quality, design and content of our Website, to analyze the use of our Website and to cooperate with law enforcement. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Except as expressly set forth herein, we will not share, rent or trade your Personal Information with third parties without your explicit permission. 

· We may use Personal Information internally – for example, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to make our Website more useful, to customize our Website and personalize its content for you. 

· Third-party vendors who provide services to us or facilitate or evaluate the Sites or Services, such as e-mail service providers sending e-mails on our behalf. We may also authorize third-party vendors or service providers to collect information on our behalf. 

· Business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services may be offered on our website or together with our software. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service because their name will appear, either alone or with ours. If you choose to use these products or services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners. If you wish to no longer allow that third party to use your information you may opt-out by contacting that third party directly. 

· In addition, by analyzing all information we receive, including all information concerning users and services, we may compile statistical information across a variety of users (“Statistical Information”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new products and services can be considered and so existing products and services can be tailored to customer desires. Statistical Information is anonymous and we will not link Statistical Information to any Personal Information. We may share Statistical Information with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion. We also use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of the Website and/or Services. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this Website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this Website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our Website and Services. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) located at<http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html> and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) located at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ Please see the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy for additional information. 

· Referring websites. If you were referred to this Website from another site (for example, through a link you clicked on another site that directed you to this one), we may share some information about you with that referring website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that referred you here. 

· Companies within our corporate family that are involved in operating or providing the Services. We may share your personal information with our affiliates. Our affiliates will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Policy, including requests that personal information not be used to provide you with Services. 

· The advertisements you see on this Website are served by us or by our service providers. But we also allow third parties to collect information about your online activities through cookies and other technologies. These third parties include (1) business partners, who collect information when you interact with one of their advertisements on our site; and (2) advertising networks, which collect information about your interests when you interact with one of the advertisements they place on various websites on the Internet. The information gathered by these third parties is used to make predictions about your interests or preferences and to display advertisements on our sites and across the Internet tailored to your apparent interests. We do not permit these third parties to collect personal information about you (such as email address) on our site, nor do we share with them any personal information about you. 

· Please note that we do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies these third parties may use to collect information about your interests, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy 

We may share aggregated or anonymous data with third parties for any use whatsoever. 

We also may share your information: 

· In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. 

· When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company or this website, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms and Conditions for the Site, and other agreements. 

· In the event that our company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our Website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information. The Website does not sell, rent or lease the personal information that you provide about yourself to third parties unless we have your consent. 

Collection of Information by Third Parties 

You are surfing a dynamically generated website that includes third-party advertising. Placement of tracking technologies such as and not limited to cookies and / or web beacons is permitted to third party advertising companies. These third party advertising companies may use such technologies to gather anonymous website statistics about your visits to this and other websites. These statistics are used by these third party advertising companies to provide ads of relevance to you. The information is gained in a statistical manner for use by us or by advertisers on our site. Data gathered will not identify you personally. It is strictly aggregate statistical data about our visitors and how they used our resources on the site. No identifying personal information will be shared at any time via cookies. 

Any of our advertisers may also have a use for cookies and may collect information in regards to your computer for our services. We a re not responsible, nor do we have control of the cookies downloaded from advertisements. They are downloaded only if you click on the advertisement. 

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from this site, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from this Website to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our Website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. 

###  Cookies FAQ 

###  Q: What Are Cookies? 

A: Cookies are text files that a web server places on your computer when you visit a web page. The cookies are used by the website to enable certain functionalities, like keeping you logged in or remembering your settings and displaying information relevant to you. 

####  Q: What kind of information to cookies contain? 

####  A: We use several types of cookies, each containing different information- 

####  1\. Anonymous analytics cookies containing anonymous aggregate statistics and analysis. 

####  2\. Registration cookies let us know when you are logged-in so that features requiring lo-in are available to you 

3\. Third party non advertising-related cookies that allow us to integrate the Website with other services like Twitter or Facebook. 

####  4\. Third-party Advertising cookies let us deliver and track advertisements that are relevant to your interests. 

####  Q: How do I turn off cookies? 

A: You can stop your browser from accepting cookies by following the instructions detailed below. Note that disabling cookies will prevent you from using certain functionalities of the Website. 

  * Safari [web version](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042) & [iOS version](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677)

Correcting or Updating your Information 

The Website allows you to view the information you provided during registration and to alter any data, inaccuracies or errors. To request such access, or correct, update, or amend your personal information please contact us at the following e-mail address: 

E-mail address: [viralwomen.com@gmail.com](mailto:viralwomen.com@gmail.com?subject=Viralwomen%20-%20Contact%20us)

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at the e-mail address, postal address, or telephone number listed above. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Communications 

We may send you email messages about us or our products and services as well as email messages about products and services of selected third parties. By accepting the Terms and Conditions for the Website (including the terms of this Privacy Policy which are incorporated therein) or using the Site or the Services, you affirmatively consent to receive such commercial messages. As a registered member, you can remove your personal information from our mailing list and to stop receiving future communication from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at [viralwomen.com@gmail.com](mailto:viralwomen.com@gmail.com?subject=Viralwomen%20-%20Contact%20us). You will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages in any such email we send. Please note that we reserve the right to send you service related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions on this site, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you cancel your account. 

Use of the Website by Children 

We not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. In the event you become aware that an individual under the age of 13 has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately. 

Games: we may provide games on our Website. In order to fully enjoy this Service, we may ask children to register and provide us with certain information, such as an email and a password. In order to register, we will require the consent of a parent and/or guardian.
